Given a sorted array consisting 0’s and 1’s. The problem is to find the index of first ‘1’ in the sorted array. It could be possible that the array consists of only 0’s or only 1’s. If 1’s are not present in the array then print “-1”.

Examples : 

Input : arr[] = {0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1}
Output : 6
Explanation: The index of first 1 in the array is 6.

Input : arr[] = {0, 0, 0, 0}
Output : -1
Explanation: 1’s are not present in the array.